# Anna Rusyayeva

Email: annarsve@gmail.com Mobile: +7(922)159-60-30

Github: https://github.com/VanillaWulf

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anna-rusyaeva-6b1276148

#### **SUMMARY**

Five years of experience in commercial development for varying business areas provided me with the skill to understand client's goals and to create tasks to achieve it. Thanks to a solid set of marketing tools, I promote the relevant customers in the right direction according to the needed intention. Moreover, with the help of excellent building communications with current teams and contractors, I clearly plan tasks and hand over projects on time.

#### **SKILLS**

- **Agile** (SCRUM, Kanban, scrumban)
- Managing projects (Trello, Jira)
- E-commerce (Yandex Direct, Yandex Metrics, Google AdWords, Google Analytics)
- Market research
- Marketing (POSM, presentations, mailings)
- Sales analytics
- User demand analysis
- Developing cases for new products/features (IDEF, UML)
- **Design** (sketch, moqups, figma, adobe products)
- Strong technical stack (HTML, CSS, JS, ReactJS, Angular, git)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Developer - Bank 'Tochka'

- User demand analysis
- Marking-up with material design
- · Creating tasks in Trello and Jira
- Making user scenario using moqups
- Creating new components on Angular 2
- Improving usability
- Participate and organization of meetings
- Support written parts

# Senior Marketing Manager - 000 'Ideco'

*October 2017 – June 2018* 

July 2018 – present time

- Launch, maintaining and updating websites
- Writing technical specifications for designers and programmers
- Monitoring tasks using Jira and Trello
- Planning budgets
- Creating roadmaps
- SMM
- Activities for attraction leads (mailings, contests, articles in popular magazines, publications in top security channels)
- Typesetting e-mail pages
- Working with mailing lists databases (collect and parsing)
- Creating POS materials



**PROJECTS** 

### **Test your security**



Marketing landing page for creating customer interest through potential threats

### **Control the traffic**



Product landing page, attracting over 1000 people per month.

#### Catalog of projects



Catalog of multi-panel house structures

#### **Domain relocation**



Domain relocation without organic traffic loses

- Sales analytics
- Making bases for cold calling
- Quarterly reports about efficiency of marketing activities

## **SEO Specialist** - Advertising Agency 'Index Art'

*January 2017 – October 2017* 

- Technical auditing (layout, structure, accessibility)
- Designing and correcting a site structure
- Writing technical specifications for revising and updating
- Over 150 closing tasks monitoring
- Creating semantics cores
- Designing and implementation metadata
- Content updating, rendering a page layout
- Creating monthly reports for customers

# Context Advertising and SEO Specialist -

December 2015 - September 2016

Advertising Agency 'ManyLetters'

- Creating and running campaigns in Yandex. Direct, Google AdWords, MyTarget
- Coordination updates with clients
- Writing specifications for programmers
- Creating monthly reports for customers

# **Software Engineer -**

October 2013 - September 2014

Special design bureau 'Peleng'

- Writing technical specification for software
- Detecting of software functionality flaws
- Revising software in C++
- Modular and integration testing

**CERTIFICATIONS** 

#### **EDUCATION**

Beijing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics Master of Computer Science

February 2015

Courses and Certificates: Build Front-End Web Apps from Scratch course

**Ural Federal University** 

2015

Master of Computer Science in Technology in Mathematical Software and Information Systems Administration

Professional HTML & CSS, level 1

**Ural Federal University** 

2013

Higher Professional Education in Legal Regulation of Business

**LANGUAGES** 

Russian native speaker English - B2

**Ural Federal University** 

2013 Bachelor of Computer Science in Technology in Design and Technology of Electronic

Means

**Mailing** 



**Products mailing** 



Newsletter for the company.

**Ice cream Store** 

